(Sheldon:)And he's terrible at it.
I always win.
-S0, you're okay with this?
-Well, why wouldn't I be?
(Amy:)Well, this project
would have us working
(Amy:)in close proximity to one another.
(Amy:)And there's the vulgar adage that one
should not defecate where one eats.
(Sheldon:)My father used to say
that all the time.
That and, "Who does one have
to orally gratify
to get a drink around here?"
(Sheldon:)But what does that have to do
with you working at the university?
(Penny:)Sheldon,
"Don't defecate where you eat,"
(Amy:)means don't have a romantic
relationship in the workplace.
(Sheldon:)Really?
(Amy:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)Huh...
(Sheldon:)I always took it literally.
(Sheldon:)That's why I have never once moved
my bowels in this or any restaurant.
(Amy:)I'm relieved that you don't have
a problem with us working together.
(Sheldon:)Not as relieved as I'm about to be.
(Sheldon:)It's a brave new world, little lady.